Guide to the Reuben A. Holden, Secretary of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- University Secretary: Subject File, 1901-1972; Series III
  - Yale and industry, 1959-1965 (Box 304, Folder 1201-1202)
  - Yale and New Haven, 1933-1967 (Box 305, Folder 1203-1207)
  - Yale and Wales
    - Brewster, Kingman, Jr., 1968 (Box 305, Folder 1208)
    - British Rail, 1968 (Box 305, Folder 1209)
    - Brown, Bruce, 1968 (Box 305, Folder 1210)
    - Eli International, 1968 (Box 305, Folder 1211)
    - Henning, Basil D., 1968 (Box 305, Folder 1212)
    - Holden, Reuben A., 1968 (Box 305, Folder 1213)
    - Maps, 1968 (Box 305, Folder 1214)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967-1969 (Box 305, Folder 1215)
    - Morley-Smith, David, 1968 (Box 306, Folder 1216)
    - Myers, Edward D., 1967-1968 (Box 306, Folder 1217)
    - Pias Gronow, Wrexham, 1968 (Box 306, Folder 1218)
  - Yale and Wales
    - Poet Laureate, 1968 (Box 306, Folder 1219)
    - Prince of Wales, 1968 (Box 306, Folder 1220)
    - Programs, 1968 (Box 306, Folder 1221)
    - Publicity, 1968 (Box 306, Folder 1222)
    - Publicity duplicates, 1968 (Box 306, Folder 1223)
    - Seton nameplate, 1968 (Box 306, Folder 1224)
    - Travel Guides, 1968 (Box 306, Folder 1225)
    - Trip expenses, 1968 (Box 306, Folder 1226)
    - University of Wales, 1968 (Box 306, Folder 1227)
    - Walker, Patrick, 1968 (Box 306, Folder 1228)
    - Wrexham, 1968-1971 (Box 306, Folder 1230-1232)
    - Wrexham Church, 1927-1968 (Box 306, Folder 1233)
    - Wrexham history, 1967-1968 (Box 306, Folder 1234)
    - Wrexham Town Clerk, 1968 (Box 307, Folder 1235)
    - Yale alumni near Wrexham, 1968 (Box 307, Folder 1236)
    - Yale Band, 1968 (Box 307, Folder 1237)
    - Yale Club of London, 1968 (Box 307, Folder 1238)
    - Yale Club of New Haven, 1968 (Box 307, Folder 1239)
    - Yale Tomb restoration, 1968 (Box 307, Folder 1240)
  - Yale Manuscripts: Thomas, Herbert
    - "Earthquake at Yale" and the Berkeley Donations, undated (Box 307, Folder 1241)
    - Pioneers in Medicine at Yale, undated (Box 307, Folder 1242-1243)
    - Samuel Seabury, Our First American Bishop, undated (Box 307, Folder 1244)
    - Yale Men and Landmarks, 1967-1970 (Box 307, Folder 1245-1248)
  - Yale miscellaneous, 1948-1965 (Box 308, Folder 1249-1254)
  - Zeta Psi, 1948-1954 (Box 309, Folder 1255-1261)
- General Correspondence and Subject File, 1901-1972; 1953-1971; Series IV
  Conditions Governing Access
  These records are available for research.
  Scope and Contents
  The files in this series (1.75 linear feet) were removed as individual items or as entire folders primarily from series II. The sensitive topics addressed within the documents prevent them from being made available for research with the other administrative files in this record unit. The documents themselves address a variety of topics related to the operations and responsibilities of the Yale Secretary's Office, 1953-1971.
  - Extracts from folders
    Restricted until January 1, 2045.
    - Admissions Office
      - 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
      - 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
    - Arts and Sciences, programs for the, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Botany Department, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Graduate School, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8-10)
    - History Department, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Institute of Far Eastern Languages, 1953-1961 (Box 1, Folder 12-14)
    - Law School
      - 1954-1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
    - Medical School, 1953-1965 (Box 1, Folder 18-20)
    - Military Science Department
      - 1955-1962 (Box 1, Folder 21-22)
      - 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Philosophy Department
      - 1951-1963 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Police, Campus, 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Political Science Department, 1954-1962 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Provost's office, 1953-1963 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Religion Department, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Sociology Department, 1953-1960 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Southeast Asia Studies, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Entire folders
    - Institute of Far Eastern Languages
      - 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 34-36)
    - Lee case, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Linguistics Department, 1957-1967 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Professorships, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Treasurer's Office
      - 1953-1963 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - 1963-1971 (Box 3, Folder 41-44)